You noticed last time, I tried to show you the importance
你们上次注意到，我试图向你们展示其重要性
of having gentleness
要温柔
because we have to work almost on a micro-crystalline field
因为我们几乎必须在一个微晶场上工作
to have a contact, let's say, almost holistic, almost global on the body.
为了获得一种可以说是整体的、全面的身体接触。
So here, first information
所以这里，第一个信息
that I'm looking for to see if there's good expansion,
我正在寻找，看看是否有良好的扩张，
it's the brain's tai chi.
这是大脑的太极。
So here, there's a bit of a lack behind.
所以这里，后面有点缺失。
That means she can get tired quickly already.
这意味着她可能已经很快感到疲劳。
So that means we need to rebalance a mesenteric axis in Mademoiselle.
所以这意味着需要重新平衡这位小姐的肠系膜轴。
I can say it here, on the plane, on the axis
我可以在这里说，在平面上，在轴线上
digestive,
消化系统，
which is perhaps a little... it will help her.
这可能有点……这会帮助她。
We're going to revitalize her body a little.
我们会稍微恢复她的身体活力。
So here, I'm going to need to go...
所以这里，我需要去……
I don't have enough magnetic force.
我没有足够的磁力。
in the brain so I'm not pushed back enough and so I'm going to see if it's
在大脑中，所以我没有被充分排斥，所以我要去看看，要么是
already a
已经是一个
purely nutritional plan but you at the cream level there you go
纯粹的营养层面，但你在头骨层面，看
you relax your hands gently I'm going to
你慢慢放松你的手，我将
show you a little bit of what I see how you work so you are very precise
给你展示一点我所看到的，你是如何工作的，所以你非常精确
but you are too precise you
但你太精确了，你
must dare to take some distance so
必须敢于保持一点距离，所以
And also a peripheral vision.
还有周边视觉。
Now, you let what's in your hand come.
现在，你让手中的东西自然出现。
You feel that we are not expanded enough.
你觉得我们不够扩张。
The first movement is an expansion.
第一个动作是扩张。
I must have this feeling of expansion.
我必须有这种扩张的感觉。
Here, I'm going to see if, by modifying here, simply an axis,
在这里，我将看看，通过简单地修改一个轴，
except that I have to search very precisely for the mesenteric axis.
只是我必须非常精确地寻找肠系膜轴。
So I put myself, in a certain way, on an embryonic remnant.
所以我以某种方式，置身于胚胎残余之上。
to see if I can help a little
看看我是否能帮上一点忙
this force.
这种力量。
There, I have to go look for it.
在那里，我必须去寻找。
Tell me if there's a change
你告诉我是否有变化
in the...
在……
I have to look for the globality.
我必须寻求整体性。
For now, that's just a level
目前，这只是一个层面
The omnispheres are searching.
全方位正在寻找。
So, there, I...
所以，在这里，我……
connect with an ancient vital energy, if you will, that the
与一种古老的生命能量相连接，如果你愿意，身体知道这种能量，大脑
body knows, that the brain
身体知道，大脑
it used. And it's simply on a vascular plane
它已经使用了。这只是在一个血管层面上
which is first an electrical field.
它首先是一个电场。
he just made an oxidative change
它刚刚发生了氧化变化
he just changed his breathing
它刚刚改变了呼吸
I'm going to change, I'm going to put it
我将改变，我将把它放在
on another level
在另一个层面
I'm going to put it on a plane
我将把它放在一个平面上
another axis
另一个轴线
it's an axis
这是一个轴线
a vestige
一个遗迹
almost phallomesenteric
几乎是阴茎系膜的
if you will
如果你愿意
It's deeper in the brain.
它在大脑深处。
It's a deeper sensation in the brain.
这是大脑深处的一种感觉。
There, we're going to look for another level.
在那里，我们将寻找另一个层面。
You note the changes.
你注意到这些变化。
Watch what's going to happen.
看看会发生什么。
What do you feel?
你有什么感觉？
It goes back deep.
它回到了深处。
There, really, it's a good fact.
在那里，这确实是一个很好的事实。
and from the depth of the brain
以及大脑的深处
4 nutritional levels
4个营养层面
what are the 4 levels
这4个层面是什么
4 pipes
4根管道
by vertebral artery
通过椎动脉
and carotid
和颈动脉
we formed the basilar trunk
我们形成了基底动脉干
there you go
就是这样
I'm just going to
我只是
it's on the back moment
它在后面
there you go so here
就是这样，所以在这里
we can already say that on
我们已经可以说
it will release here
它会在这里释放
we're going to release a plane for her
我们将为他释放一个平面
watch what's going to happen
看看会发生什么
I'm going to release her
我将为他释放
it's going to get hot in the head a bit
头部会有点发热
is that okay for you?
这对你来说可以吗？
you'll see what happens
你会看到会发生什么
and there we are on a subtle level
我们现在处于一个微妙的层面
there you go that's
就是这样
how I work
我就是这样工作的
there I'm in cellular
我现在处于细胞层面
I'm in glial
我处于神经胶质层面
yeah deep
是的，在深层
I'm going to release a level
我将释放一个层面
you say a word that comes to me, should I say it or what?
你说一个词，如果我想到了，我就说出来，是吗？
truth. There you go, that will do you good, young lady, madam.
真相。好了，这会对您有好处，小姐，女士。
Diaphragm here which is a bit disturbed.
这里的膈肌有点紊乱。
First diaphragm. There you go, you see, describe a bit your
第一个膈肌。好了，你看，描述一下你的
feeling? Yes, it shocks a lot and then I felt it untie,
感受？是的，它非常震惊，然后我感觉到它正在解开，
especially here.
尤其是在这里。
And also a sensation in the mouth. The tongue and
嘴里也有感觉。舌头和
the heart bud. There you go,
心脏的萌芽。好了，
that
这
will revitalize your closed circuits a bit, that will do you good. Someone
会稍微激活您体内封闭的回路，这会对您有好处。有人